lexusfinancial.com 2009-03-27

# Lexus Financial: Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

Lexus Financial Services Privacy Policy And Terms Of Use  
  
Effective as of February 12, 2007

This page contains the online privacy policy and terms of use applicable to your usage of this website and lexusfinancialofsc.com.

Privacy Statement  
Normal Website Usage  
Collection and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information  
You May Request A Copy of Your Privacy Policy  
Your Choices  
Changes To Our Policy  
Accuracy of Your Information  
Confidentiality and Security  
Assistance for Victims of Identity Theft  
Terms of Use  
Questions, Comments or Complaints

 **Privacy Statement**  
  
Lexus Financial Services, Toyota Motor Credit Corporation, Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc., and their subsidiaries (LFS, or we) respect your privacy and the confidential nature of the information that we gather during the course of our relationship with you. This Policy describes Lexus Financial Services' policy regarding information received about you during visits to our website.  
  
 **Normal Website Usage**  
  
You can visit Lexus Financial Services' website to read product, investment, and company information, or use some of our online tools (e.g., What's Right for Me? and Payment Estimator) without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. During these types of visits, we collect and store statistical information on an anonymous basis, such as the information about the time and length of your visit, the website you last visited, the pages you request, and the date and time of those requests. We may also collect and store the name of your Internet Service Provider.

We use cookies when you enter our website to help us gather this type of statistical information. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes so that we can track website and user activity. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at most websites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, if you do so, some parts of our website may not work properly for you.

We also use cookies to trigger certain online customer service surveys, which could be hosted on a site other than this site. These surveys are completely anonymous and optional. The information that LFS and any outside survey company obtain from you if you choose to fill out these surveys is used only to improve your experience in visiting the LFS website.

 **Collection and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**  
  
There are instances where we request personally identifiable information to provide our website visitors a service or correspondence (e.g., promotions and mailed brochures). This information, such as name, mailing address, email address, or type of request, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data and used to fulfill your request. If you are our customer, the information may also be shared as described below.

When you submit an online application to us or you are accessing your account online, we collect the following types of personally identifiable information about you:

  * Information that is required for you to register and logon to My LFS Account, such as your account number, email address, vehicle identification number, social security number, and ZIP code; and
  * Information we receive from you on applications for credit or other forms, such as your contact information, assets and income; and
  * Information we receive from you about your transactions with us, or affiliates (as permitted by law), or others such as account balances, payment history or account activity.

Credit applications and consumer report information: We do not disclose personally identifiable information from your credit application to any third parties, including our affiliates, except as permitted by law. We also collect information from consumer reporting agencies, but we do not disclose personally identifiable consumer report information to any third parties, including our affiliates, except as permitted by law.

If you are our customer, to the extent permitted by law and in accordance with our Privacy Policy, the personally identifiable information we collect about you may be shared with our affiliates and nonaffiliated third parties as follows:

  * Financial products service providers, such as Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc. and Toyota Financial Savings Bank.
  * Non-financial companies engaged in the distribution, marketing, and sales of Lexus and Toyota automobiles, such as Toyota Motor Sales U.S.A., Inc., authorized Lexus and Toyota dealerships and other dealerships with which we have a business relationship, independent Lexus and Toyota dealerships' marketing associations, private Toyota distributors, nonaffiliated third parties calling us for information about your account with us, and nonaffiliated third parties who may sell your data in aggregate form for automotive marketing purposes.
  * Companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements.

We do not sell the collected data, regardless of whether you are a LFS customer.  
  
 **You May Request A Copy of Your Privacy Policy**  
  
LFS continuously strives to comply with all applicable federal and state privacy laws. Some policies will vary by territory, based on the applicable laws of the region. If you are a customer of LFS, you may request a copy of your Financial Privacy Notice (if applicable) by calling us at  
1-888-717-9248. LFS insurance customers may request a copy of their Insurance Privacy Notice (if applicable) by calling us at 1-800-448-1505.  
  
 **Your Choices**  
  
Financial customers of Lexus Financial Services have certain privacy options that are provided pursuant to applicable federal and state privacy laws. To learn more about your privacy options, refer to the Financial Privacy Notice mailed to you, or call us at 1-888-717-9248.  
  
 **Changes To Our Policy**  
  
As permitted by law, we may change this policy and provide notice by posting a revised policy on this site. By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this website after a revised policy has been posted signifies your acceptance of the revised policy.  
  
 **Accuracy of Your Information**  
  
You may contact us at 1-800-874-7050 regarding the accuracy, completeness and substance of the information collected about you while you are on this website.  
  
 **Confidentiality and Security**  
  
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees and other persons hired by us who need to know the information to provide products and services to you and to otherwise service your account(s) with us. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

If you choose to complete and submit our Online Credit Application, or to access "My LFS Account", your personal information will be protected during transmission by an encryption process.

 **Assistance for Victims of Identity Theft**  
  
If you believe that your account has been subject to unauthorized access, please call us immediately at 1-800-874-7050. You may also contact your local law enforcement agency, and the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). You may speak with an FTC counselor by calling toll-free, 1-877-IDTheft (1-877-438-4338). Or, to enter information about you complaint to a FTC online database, sign on to [www.consumer.gov/idtheft/](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/microsites/idtheft/).  
  
 **Terms of Use**  
  
In addition to the terms of use contained on this page, supplemental terms of use may appear on specific pages of the website. This website contains information regarding Lexus Financial Services, Toyota Motor Credit Corporation, Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc., and Toyota Motor Sales, U.S.A., Inc. (jointly, "Toyota") and their products and promotional programs. Toyota Motor Credit Corporation, Toyota Motor Insurance Services, Inc., and their subsidiaries are collectively referred to as "LFS" throughout this website.

We are not responsible for errors or negligent use of the services offered by this website, including input errors, negligent handling or sharing of passwords, and leaving a computer unattended while accessing the Online Credit Application or the Manage Account section of the website.

While we make all reasonable efforts to ensure that all material on this website is correct, accuracy cannot be guaranteed. Balance or payment information that appears on My LFS Account assumes all payments posted to your account were valid postings made with good funds. This website may contain hypertext links to other websites that are completely independent of this website. We do not assume responsibility as to the accuracy, completeness, or authenticity of the information presented on any website accessed via such a link. A link to another entity's website should not be construed as endorsement by LFS of such entity's website, products, or services.

All of the content presented on this website is for information purposes only and in no way creates any fiduciary relationship between you and LFS; you should seek appropriate tax, financial, or legal advice when necessary. No content on this site constitutes an offer to buy or sell Lexus vehicles, nor does it constitute an offer of a direct loan or lease. All finance and insurance programs described in this website are available to qualified applicants only through Lexus Financial Services and participating Lexus dealers. All programs are subject to change or termination at any time. Final terms of purchase or lease are set by you and your Lexus dealer. The information contained on this website is protected by copyright and may not be reproduced without our written consent.

 **Questions, Comments or Complaints**   
  
If you have questions, comments or complaints regarding this policy or the terms of use, contact us 1-888-717-9248.
